let questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",
    options: [
      " A.Standard notation",
      " B.Tab notation",
      " C.Morse code notation",
      "D.Graphics notation",
    ],
    answer: "C.Morse code notation",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What is the most common time signature in classical music?",
    options: ["A.3/4", "B.4/4", "C.5/4", "D.6/8"],
    answer: "B.4/4",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",
    options: ["A.Violin", "B.Piano", "C.Harp", "D.Theremin"],
    answer: "D.Theremin",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is the most common key in pop music?",
    options: ["A.C Major", "B.G Major", "C.D Major", "D.A Major"],
    answer: "A.C Major",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of chord?",
    options: ["A.Major", "B.Minor", "C.Diminished", "D.Flat"],
    answer: "D.Flat",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",
    options: ["A.Jazz", "B.Blues", "C.Rock", "D.Applesauce"],
    answer: "D.Applesauce",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",
    options: ["A.Harmony", "B.Counterpoint", "C.Form", "D.Cooking"],
    answer: "D.Cooking",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",
    options: ["A.Allegro", "B.Andante", "C.Adagio", "D.Moderato"],
    answer: "A.Allegro",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",
    options: ["A.Sonata", "B.Symphony", "C.Concerto", "D.Spaghetti"],
    answer: "D.Spaghetti",
    category: "music",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",
    options: ["A.Sibelius", "B.Finale", "C.MuseScore", "D.Microsoft Word"],
    answer: "D.Microsoft Word",
    category: "music",
  },
];
